<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HLC Advising Initiative</title>
    <link>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HLC Advising Initiative</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright Truman State University</copyright><atom:link href="http://vieker.github.io/hlc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Announcement: Advising Handbook Forthcoming</title>
      <link>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/posts/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/posts/overview/</guid>
      <description>[Content about the Advising Handbook.]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background</title>
      <link>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/background/</guid>
      <description>(This will all be fleshed out into prose, including an explanation of how the Subcommittee work informed the Task Groups, who in turn are sequenced so that their work informs future task groups.)
HLC  Regional accreditor Three &amp;ldquo;pathways&amp;rdquo; to accreditation We&amp;rsquo;re on the &amp;ldquo;Open Pathway&amp;rdquo; Quality Intiative = Advising 10-year accreditation cycle Final report due June 1, 2024  Why advising?  Advising affects retention Chance to develop a formalized, unified approach  What has been done so far?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview: Truman&#39;s HLC Advising Initiative</title>
      <link>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/posts/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Start here for an introduction to Truman&amp;rsquo;s Advising initiative. You can also see who at Truman is contributing to this project, as well as a timeline for its completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/people/</guid>
      <description>(For each group, I will add a link to their finished work.)
Task Groups Syllabus and Communication Task Group Spring 2022
 Andrea Maag, CAE Jana Arabas, HES Jeffrey Vittengl, PSYC  Learning Outcomes Task Group Fall 2021
 Jenny Marcus, CAE Dave Lusk, Career Center Priscilla Riggle, ENG Karen Vittengl, PSYC  Tenure and Promotion Task Group Fall 2021
 Tim Walston, SAM Amber Johnson, SOAN/JUST Nancy Daley Moore, HES  Mission Statement Task Group Spring 2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeline</title>
      <link>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vieker.github.io/hlc/timeline/</guid>
      <description>(This be updated and made more readable.)
 Fall 2020  subcommittees established subcommittee charges finalized preliminary recommendations drafted (a formal document produced by each subcommittee)   Spring 2021 (NSSE administered, FSSE administered and results returned)  preliminary recommendations reviewed by Steering Committee preliminary recommendations sent to Governance   Summer 2021  incorporate feedback on preliminary recommendation   Fall 2021 (NSSE results returned)  develop implementation procedures   Spring 2022 (NSSE administered)  develop implementation procedures   Summer 2022  communicate implementation procedures   Fall 2022 (NSSE results returned)  deploy implementation procedures   Spring 2023 (NSSE Administered, FSSE administered and results returned)  test implementation procedures   Summer 2023 Fall 2023 (NSSE results returned)  test implementation procedures   Spring 2024  draft final report    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
